It was right around the time when the music was shifting from pop to pop, so it made a big impression on me.
I had a great impression of the singer.
Yes?
Let's go. We're not together.
Ha-ha-ha-ha...
Hm?
What?
I came in on the way.
I didn't stop.
You got a sudden appearance, didn't you?
I didn't resign.
Yes, I did.
That's why...
Yes.
The Olympics...
Oh!
Finally, the Paris Olympics.
Yes
Bonjour, France, everyone!
Come on, come on, come on...
S'il vous plaît.
What does that mean?
S'il vous plait?
I think it means something like...
I think it means something like "How are you?
How are you? something like that.
Silvplay.
The Olympics are held every four years.
The last one was in Tokyo.
Due to the Corona disaster
Because of the Corona disaster.
So it's been three years.
Not four years.
That's why it feels a little early.
How about the Olympics?
Do you watch?
But you're going to watch, right? Eh, but you watch it.
What did I see last year?
I saw something.
Round and round and round
Gong, gong, gong...
Do you understand?
Yes, I see it.
It's a hammer throw.
Round and round and round.
Gong! Gong!
Isn't that amazing?
It's amazing, isn't it?
When I see it, I always think...
"What if that thing comes off?
What if it comes off and hits a square?
You know, there are referees and such.
Yes, it's dangerous.
Ah, come here.
Bonjour.
Silvplay!
S'il vous plaît!
Silvuplay.
S'il vous plait
Bordeaux
Bordeaux?
I believe it's called Bordeaux.
It's famous for its wine.
What do you think of the Olympics?
It's been a while.
What are the main events?
I don't know.
But I liked swimming.
Oh, yeah?
It's kind of fun, isn't it?
To go like this like a fish.
It's a little bit more human.
It's a bit different than it used to be. Compared to a little while ago
Japanese swimmers
Swimming
You've become stronger, haven't you?
I'm getting stronger.
Really.
When I was young...
I was not even close to them.
There was one guy, Daichi Suzuki, in the backstroke.
Men's.
In the first place...
He won a gold medal in the Vassallo.
And he won the gold medal.
The Japanese were so excited.
But overall, it's going up.
Recently... a while ago...
Kosuke Kitajima was the first.
I can't say anything else.
I know.
Was it "Seriously?
For real?
Seriously?
Are you serious?
That's what everyone seems to be saying.
What was that?
For real?
I'm not supposed to say anything.
I can't say anything.
And there was one more thing.
It feels super good.
It feels good.
Watch out.
That feels so good.
That feels good.
That's what I'm talking about.
There's even a quote. I even got some great quotes out of it.
And then, of course, there's that...
Swimming, track and field...
And ball sports.
Really...
Japan has become strong, hasn't it?
Table tennis, for example.
Table Tennis
Sapper.
Volleyball
Volleyball.
Volleyball. - Volleyball.
Soccer.
All kinds of stuff.
No, no, no.
It's not really a gesture corner, but...
You know what I mean.
You don't have to do that.
You have to do it.
Volleyball, it's usually like this.
Like this, like this, like this.
Like this.
Yes, sir.
By all means, by all means.
I don't know.
Yeah.
There's a lot of drama.
Yes...
Then there will be one this year too.
Yes, there will be.
So there's gymnastics and stuff.
Wow!
Right?
What about the competition for Ms. Ankura?
You know...
uh...that (something mentioned before which is distant psychologically or in terms of time)
that (something mentioned before which is distant psychologically or in terms of time)
total (esp. of units of land area equal to one-tenth of a tsubo)
s (pluralizing suffix)
Well, you know...
In other words...
So there is.
I'm looking forward to it.
Yes, yes, yes.
Well, anyway...
Well, let's get started.
Yes, yes, yes.
I'd like to write to you...
ah... ah... ah...
This is it...
This corner
This, this...
Eh, eh, eh, eh.
what's wrong?
what's going on?
What's going on?
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Look at all these creatures!
In French, it's "Let's see the creatures!
It's all in Japanese!
Indeed, it's all perfectly Japanese!
Not a single foreign word in it!
So, Mr. Hyakushiki-kun sent it to me!
Thank you very much!
Miura City, Kanagawa Prefecture
Oba Master, whose liveliness is unparalleled in the world!
Thank you very much!
Ria, who has no equal in freshness
Mr. Bite of Ebichu who has nothing to compare in splendor!
Good evening Good evening.
I'm sorry to have to do this.
May I have your attention, creatures of creation?
Yes, sir.
Hoki!
Hoki?
It's like the strong one from the Sword of the North Star.
Simple.
Two letters.
Hoki.
I wonder what it is.
Not a clue, but...
But this guy just sent us a picture of a hoki.
He sent us a picture of the hoki.
Correct.
So we're close.
I'm familiar with it, but...
I've never seen it.
Wow.
You know what?
Think about your reaction.
You've been doing this for a long time.
You've been doing reflections for a long time.
What's this?
I've never heard that voice before.
Huh?
I was wondering why.
A little more... pitter-patter.
Pitter-patter.
Why?
What do you mean, "Why?
That's the first time I've heard that.
Wow, first time.
Hoki?
I've never heard of it.
A little rakugo... A Little Bit of Rakugo
Rakugo
I think I'm going to say "oye" just like that.
You really have no idea what you're talking about, do you?
Me neither, by the way.
I've only vaguely heard of him.
But I've never seen him.
I've only heard of him.
I don't know...
I don't understand why it's in the deep sea...
The deep sea and the sky...
Surprisingly, they're pretty close to us these days.
You can take pictures of them, right?
That's true.
Well, you know, up in the sky...
There's also the deep sea.
Well, there are many places.
I can't say I've ever seen anything like that.
Creatures have been discovered in many places.
Hoki.
Hokey.
What does it look like?
It's like this.
I thought it might be rice cake if you said something like that
Hohoho
Hoho
In the style of Kuniya Tanaka
Hohohoto
Hohhot
A little bit of this
Hot
10 hot
Not yet.
Where the hell are you going?
You've been doing it all along. You've been doing it all along.
You've been doing it for a long time.
All I could say was, "We're still here.
Okay...
Hotchkiss.
hoki!
Hokey!
I wonder what kind of creature it is.
He's writing with a brush, isn't he?
You know how you write on the flip side with this magic marker?
I love that sound.
I can listen to it all the time.
Like a blackboard.
I don't like those keys on the blackboard.
Of course not.
squeak squeak squeak squeak squeak squeak squeak squeak squeak squeak squeak
I like this one.
When you're playing basketball in the gym or something, you hear this kind of sound, right?
I know.
That's cool.
Is it called a writer's book?
Writer's book?
Writer's sound!
Writer's tone!
Writer! It's like a rubbing.
Okay, so...
So, can we go to Gan-chan now?
Yes, Gan-chan!
I'll take care of it.
HOKI!
That's what it says.
It's got "hohki" written all over it.
I think it's a "ho" coming out of here.
Amazing.
It's a little too simple.
I don't know.
Anyway...
I'm just trying to figure out the kanji for "ho".The Chinese character for "Ho".
Please try to express it.
Yes, I tried to express it.
I see.
By the way, what kind of creature is this in the image?
For example, on land?
That's it. It's a lion.
A lion?
Yes, yes.
I was like, "Well, if it's a lion, maybe I can take a picture of it like this.
I wonder if I could take a picture of it.
It's pretty imminent.
It's pretty much a lion.
Wait a minute.
A lion has a name, right?
So, Hoki is just another name for lion?
That's right.
I see.
Yes.
It's a bit Luigi-like.
Luigi.
Luigi Luigi.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
It's a new word.
Wait a minute.
It means they're very similar.
Yes, they are.
Very similar.
Not just Luigi.
Yes, Luigi Luigi.
He's almost a lion, but...
I'm doing Luigi Luigi Luigi.
Luigi Luigi Luigi.
I see. I see.
That's new.
Well then, doctor, please... So, please, doctor.
Here you go, sir.
Bang.
Oh, well, which one is it?
Oh, I see... I see...
It grows on a tree.
Yeah.
Is it like a branch?
It's different from the seven stars.
It's a septum.
Yes.
Vajrasattva.
Like a branch.
Like that.
broom
Yes, yes, yes.
It's an insect that looks like a broomstick.
You said "broomstick".
I was saying "broomstick," but it's some kind of dialect.
Hokey-hokey.
Like, "I got a hoki, hoki, hoki, hoki.
I think it's an insect.
So this whole thing is just...
Yes, it is.
It's a hoki.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
That makes a lot of sense for a teacher.
For a teacher.
For a teacher, that's a bit of a stretch.
No, no, it makes a lot of sense.
I'm sure he's out there.
I'm sure there are.
That's why I think you're right.That's why I thought I'd hit it.
Well, by the way, the first thing you need to do is take a look at the picture.
Yes, I want to see it.
Mr. Hyakushiki sent it to me, so let's take a look.
The correct answer is...
Let's see...
This is it.
What?
This...
Bento?
This is hoki...
Fry, fry, fry!
Fleece.
It's a hoki.
Hmm?
And when he said he succeeded in capturing it...
I think he might be talking about this.
Huh? Hmm?
No.
Yes, that's right.
Yes, yes, yes.
Hmm?
Hoki.
Yes, sir.
This is hoki.
Hmm?
This one.
That's the hoki.
This is the meat of a hoki.
Fish?
Fish.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Fried.
By the way, this really doesn't make any sense.
I didn't expect it to come out cooked.
I'm all surprised now. Now I'm all surprised!
This is what it looked like before it was cooked
Let's see...
I'd say it's about 120 centimeters long.
I'd say it's about this big... or a little bigger.
120 centimeters?
Yes, 1 meter 20
Big, big, big.
It's long and thin.
Yes.
It's... it's... it's... it's...
Um...
I hear it's used as a white fish in all sorts of things.
Yes...
Hoki...
Surprisingly...
Yes...
So it's like horse mackerel or fried horse mackerel.
I see.
It's also used for various edible purposes, like fried white fish.
Oh!
I see...
Hoki.
There are a lot of fish, aren't there?
Yes, there are.
And fish have many aliases, don't they?
That's right.
They are called differently by different fishermen in different regions.
And "Success Fish"...
Names change.
Yes, yellowtail. You know yellowtail, right?
Yes.
There are so many names... since he was a little boy.
I don't know...
Buri is when he's an adult and wears a tie to work...
In human terms...In human terms, you know.
And before that, you know, when you're wearing a T-shirt that's a little too flashy or something...
You know, when you're a little geeky.
Wearing pants that are too loose, like, "Ya-sus!
Ya-sus.
His name is different.
He's a fish of the future, right?
Oh, that's difficult.
I see... how many other names are there besides "yellowtail"?
Wow, a study corner!
What kind of things are there?
Here comes the study corner!
Buri...
What was it again?
There are a lot of things here.
There are a lot of things, aren't there?
I've heard that before.
Yes, sir.
Let's see, at first...
This is easy to understand.
I see...
You see it like this?
The first one...
The first one is called "young" or "winged".
When he was a little boy.
Like a kindergartener.
Like this.
Like he pooped his pants.
I was still like this at that time.
I didn't say that in the Heisei era.
And then
Hachimachi
Maybe
Inada
This is probably around junior high school age This is probably around middle school age?
That's right.
When I entered junior high school, my voice suddenly changed.
He used to say "whee!" but now he says...
I used to say "eeeee" but now I sound like "daaah".
It's true, it flips right back.
He also changed his rebellious phase.
When he stopped talking to his mother and father.
This is Hamachi and Inada, right?
And then from high school to 20 years old.
Mejiro
Oh!
Or Warasa.
Mejiro, right.
Or "warasa.
At this size, it's almost impossible to touch it with your neck.
Oh!
Oh, wow.
They're getting bigger.
Well, I guess high school will be like that.
He was a bit of a rebel in middle school.
In high school...
I joined a dance team and started doing rap music.
And to some extent...
yah yo yah yo
I was saying, "Chekeracchoo.
I didn't have any talent.
So I started job hunting.
And then I started going to work, and it was like, "Bri, yeah, this is a really epic growth story.
I was growing up when I started wearing a tie, you know?
It's a great story, like Buri, who, where, how, how, for example, what, how, how, how...
Who decides what's the difference between yellowtail and yellowtail?
They call it yellowtail and ship it, so there's some kind of standard, right?
I don't know, I guess you didn't know that it was called yellowtail, but you called it yellowtail, but it's actually green...
I don't know.
Well, well, well, well, well, I said yes.
I said yes. I said yes, so...
I said yes, thank you very much.
I'd like to send you something interesting related to fish or marine products.
Thank you for the night commuter train to Suginami Ward, Tokyo. I heard there's a convenience store in Osaka... called Takomusu.
I heard they have "takomusu" at the convenience store in Osaka station.
That's right!
But the octopus is a takoyaki!
Takomusu is a combination of takoyaki and omusubi.
Takoyaki and omusubi are
Like carbohydrates on carbohydrates.
That's right.
Amazing!
carbonated watermelon turnip mash mash mash mash mash
carbonated watermelon and watermelon head and head and head and head
carbs on carbs on carbs on carbs on carbs
charcoal watermelon squash squabble
Wow, this food is amazing!
The package is already!
I thought it was an octopus rice ball.
But actually, it's like this inside.
Let's see...
Well, there's rice under here.
Wrapped in seaweed.
Looks delicious!
Looks good, right?
That's interesting, I've never heard of that before.
I knew that Osaka people are really...
They eat rice with takoyaki and okonomiyaki.
I'll eat it with rice.
It's like, "I'm going to eat rice with takoyaki and okonomiyaki.
Yes.
And once, a person from the Kanto region must have stuck his head in...
I said, "What's that? That's just like charcoal charcoal pancakes and kabobs!
I said, "You guys eat ramen and ramen
You guys can't eat ramen and rice together!
He said
I heard it's like ramen and rice.
I seeOh, I see.
Oh, I see.
I'll say it this way.
But it's not for me to know, is it?
You know...
What?
That's amazing!
Osaka is indeed the capital of Japan!
Wow, it looks so good!
Maybe it's mayonnaise.
Wow!
It definitely goes well with it.
It's hot, right?
And this mayonnaise is really good.
It's delicious, isn't it?
It's a unique mayonnaise.
It smells amazing!
I love it!
Looks delicious.
I'd like to try it.
I'd love to try it!
It's true that takoyaki and rice go well together.
Yes, indeed.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Well, well, well, well...
Well then, everyone who's watching the live broadcast today...
Yes, yes, yes.
What do you think?
Ganban-ni's been on a rampage today.
No, no, no, really...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
I left my mark.
Oh, wow!
That's great
Today Well, today...
Every time I come here, it's like this, you know?
Yes, I understand.
It's like it's getting more and more and more.
Yes, yes, yes.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Well... since we're here...
What do you think?
A little...
How's everyone doing lately?
Are you having fun?
I wonder...
Are you having a happy and exciting life?
If you're not...
If you're not... then by all means, be happy.
I'm sure you are.
Yes.
Happy, happy, happy, happy.
Yes, ma'am.
Yes?
I'm rakiraki happy.
Yes.
What kind of place is that?
Dig it.
Dig it!
What's rakiraki happy?
No, but I kind of lost my voice a while back.
What?
I lost my voice.
When?
When I went to Niigata...
Ah...
Yes, when I went to Niigata.
When I went to Niigata...
I went to Niigata.
When I went to Niigata When I went away...
I crushed her voice.
Yes, yes, yes.
Well...
You said you were going to Niigata.
Yes, he said he was going to Niigata for work.
So it was just recently.
Just recently.
Yes.
About a week ago.
Oh.
I mean...
I'm so happy to be able to talk about it.
I'm happy, happy, happy.
Well, well, well, well, well, well, you're right.
I have something I really want to tell you...
but my voice is...
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Oh, no, thank you.
Yeah.
Uh huh.
So I'm happy to talk like this.
That's true.
It's true... the things we do that we take for granted...
I'm shocked when I can't do it anymore.
It's really frustrating.
You know...
I told you I've been walking a lot lately, right?
Yes, I have.
What made you do it in the first place?
I caused it once.
Yeah.
I messed up my knee.
Yes.
When I couldn't walk at all, I was so stressed.
I wondered why I wasn't even walking.
That's right.Yes, I know.
And I was so happy to see him walking when he got better.
Yeah.
That's great.
I'm alive now.
On the walkie
Yay!
It was a lot of fun.
It's important to take things for granted, isn't it?
So we're happy, happy, happy, happy.
We're happy, happy, happy.
Thank you very much.
Thanks to you. Thanks to you.
Thanks to you, thanks to you, thanks to you, thanks to you.
And now, finally, for the last time... and I don't know if some of you are going to sleep after this, but...
I don't know if some of you are going to bed after this, but I'd like to end with a bang.
I don't know if some of you are going to sleep after this, but I'll give you one last shot, and then I'll go like this.
I wish you all a very happy holiday.
Se-no, to Genta!
Fire!
Next week, we'll be broadcasting live from 7:00 p.m.
That's an hour earlier than usual.
That's early!